//Classification / Odd One Out
export const classificationSet: Topic = {
  topic: "Classification / Odd One Out",
  level: "Medium-Hard",
  totalQuestions: 20,
  totalScore: 200,
  totalTime: 30,
  questions: [
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Apple, Mango, Banana, Carrot",
      choices: ["Apple", "Mango", "Banana", "Carrot"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Carrot"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: 2, 4, 6, 9",
      choices: ["2", "4", "6", "9"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["9"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Cat, Dog, Lion, Sparrow",
      choices: ["Cat", "Dog", "Lion", "Sparrow"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sparrow"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Rose, Lotus, Lily, Mango",
      choices: ["Rose", "Lotus", "Lily", "Mango"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Mango"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: 8, 27, 64, 125",
      choices: ["8", "27", "64", "125"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["27"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Table, Chair, Sofa, Shirt",
      choices: ["Table", "Chair", "Sofa", "Shirt"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Shirt"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: 7, 11, 13, 15",
      choices: ["7", "11", "13", "15"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["15"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Iron, Gold, Silver, Cotton",
      choices: ["Iron", "Gold", "Silver", "Cotton"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Cotton"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Monday, Friday, Sunday, August",
      choices: ["Monday", "Friday", "Sunday", "August"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["August"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Knife, Fork, Spoon, Plate",
      choices: ["Knife", "Fork", "Spoon", "Plate"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Plate"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Square, Circle, Triangle, Cube",
      choices: ["Square", "Circle", "Triangle", "Cube"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Cube"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Mercury, Venus, Earth, Sun",
      choices: ["Mercury", "Venus", "Earth", "Sun"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sun"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Cat, Goat, Dog, Whale",
      choices: ["Cat", "Goat", "Dog", "Whale"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Whale"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: 21, 35, 49, 55",
      choices: ["21", "35", "49", "55"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["55"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Oxygen, Nitrogen, Helium, Coal",
      choices: ["Oxygen", "Nitrogen", "Helium", "Coal"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Coal"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Guitar, Violin, Flute, Drum",
      choices: ["Guitar", "Violin", "Flute", "Drum"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Flute"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Square, Rectangle, Parallelogram, Sphere",
      choices: ["Square", "Rectangle", "Parallelogram", "Sphere"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Sphere"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Red, Blue, Green, White",
      choices: ["Red", "Blue", "Green", "White"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["White"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Pen, Pencil, Chalk, Book",
      choices: ["Pen", "Pencil", "Chalk", "Book"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Book"],
      score: 10,
    },
    {
      question: "Find the odd one out: Horse, Tiger, Elephant, Parrot",
      choices: ["Horse", "Tiger", "Elephant", "Parrot"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswers: ["Parrot"],
      score: 10,
    }
  ]
}